academicdresshire.co.nz 2018-01-28

# Privacy Policy | Academic Dress Hire | Graduation & Academic Regalia

**Introduction**

**1\. Collection of Information**  
**2\. Use of personal information**  
**3\. Disclosure of personal information**  
**4\. Data quality/ access**

The collection, use, storage, disclosure and correction of personal information by the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire is governed by The Privacy Act 1993. Personal information means information about an identifiable individual.

The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire complies with the obligations of the Privacy Act 1993.

The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire collects, stores and uses and discloses personal information about individuals in a number of circumstances set out below.

##### 1\. Collection of Information

The following information is recorded and logged by the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire server when you visit this website:

  * your browser's Internet address;
  * your server's address;
  * your domain name;
  * your IP address
  * the date and time of your visit to the site;
  * the pages you accessed and documents downloaded;
  * the previous site visited;
  * the type of browser you are using; and
  * the user name entered if accessing a restricted site

The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire uses this information for statistical purposes and for system administration tasks to maintain this service. The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire does not attempt to identify individuals as part of regular business practice. However, in the event of an investigation, the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire, a law enforcement agency or other government agency may exercise its legal authority to inspect relevant server logs.

**Confidential and personal information**  
The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire takes all reasonable precautions to guard against unauthorised access to confidential and personal information including the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information held by the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire on its servers. When personal information is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected it may be deleted.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a very small text file that is sent to your browser from our web server and stored on your computer hard drive. The text file is sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies help us to provide the user with a customised experience without having to remind us of his/her preferences each time he/she returns to our web pages. Cookies cannot damage files, nor can they read information from the hard drive of a computer. It is possible to disable the acceptance of cookies by your web browser. However, doing so may restrict your ability to access some web pages.

##### 2\. Use of personal information

Personal information you supply to us through the use of online forms, email, online surveys and feedback will be used for the purposes of the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire including student administration matters, provision of services and the dissemination of information to staff, prospective and current students and remaining in contact with graduates.  

##### 3\. Disclosure of personal information

Personal information held by the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire will only be disclosed to third parties with your consent unless the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire is obliged to disclose information in certain circumstances set out in the Act or by order of any Court of Tribunal of competent jurisdiction.

If at any stage you provide us with your email address either as part of a message or by completing a web form, we will only use your email address for the purposes for which it was provided. We will not subscribe your email address to any external mailing list without your consent.

External sites that are linked to or from the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire site are generally not under the control or responsibility of the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire and you are advised to review their privacy statement.

##### 4\. Data quality/access

The Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire will use reasonable endeavors to maintain accurate, up-to-date information regarding students and staff.

If you believe that the personal information the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire holds about you is inaccurate and requires correction or if you require copies of your personal information held by the Kate Edger Educational Charitable Trust t/a Academic Dress Hire, please contact us by email: manager@kateedgertrust.org.nz
